<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Configuration on Uitsmijter Documentation</title>
    <link>https://docs.uitsmijter.io/configuration/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Configuration on Uitsmijter Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://docs.uitsmijter.io/configuration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Helm configuration</title>
      <link>https://docs.uitsmijter.io/configuration/helm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.uitsmijter.io/configuration/helm/</guid>
      <description>Helm configuration parameters Uitsmijter is best to install over helm.&#xA;helm repo add uitsmijter https://charts.uitsmijter.io/ helm update To list available versions run:&#xA;helm search repo uitsmijter To see a list with release candidates included:&#xA;helm search repo uitsmijter --devel The complete Values.yaml is presented first, than the parameters are described as on overview. For detailed information please read the quick start guide.&#xA;Full Values.yaml namespaceOverride: &amp;#34;&amp;#34; image: repository: ghcr.io/uitsmijter/uitsmijter # Overrides the image tag whose default is the chart appVersion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entities</title>
      <link>https://docs.uitsmijter.io/configuration/entities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.uitsmijter.io/configuration/entities/</guid>
      <description>Entities This document describes the different entities Uitsmijter uses internally. They are mentioned throughout the rest of the documentation. For a complete list of used terminology, see Terminology.&#xA;Tenant A tenant is the highest order entity in the system. Every tenant is isolated in its functions and can not share resources.&#xA;Every Tenant does have its own set of settings, providers and clients. Let&amp;rsquo;s have a look what this means in practice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tenant and client configuration</title>
      <link>https://docs.uitsmijter.io/configuration/tenant_client_config/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.uitsmijter.io/configuration/tenant_client_config/</guid>
      <description>Tenant and client configuration Uitsmijter&amp;rsquo;s goal is to offer you a login solution that can be adapted to your needs in the best possible way without prescribing the architecture of the user interface, and that can be implemented extremely elegantly and quickly. In order to set up a new system with Uitsmijter or to integrate Uitsmijter into an existing system, settings are necessary that describe the desired system landscape and the surrounding environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Logging</title>
      <link>https://docs.uitsmijter.io/configuration/logging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.uitsmijter.io/configuration/logging/</guid>
      <description>Logging The Uitsmijter authorisation server logs in different levels and formats. As default, it logs in INFO and plain strings onto the console but ndjson format is also supported.&#xA;The default might change in the future because ndjson is more commonly used.&#xA;Setting the level The following levels are available:&#xA;Name Description trace Appropriate for messages that contain information normally of use only when tracing the execution of a program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JWT Signing Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://docs.uitsmijter.io/configuration/jwt_algorithms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.uitsmijter.io/configuration/jwt_algorithms/</guid>
      <description>JWT Signing Algorithms Uitsmijter supports two JWT signing algorithms for access tokens: HS256 (HMAC with SHA-256) and RS256 (RSA with SHA-256). This guide explains the differences between these algorithms and how to migrate from HS256 to RS256.&#xA;Algorithm Comparison Feature HS256 (Symmetric) RS256 (Asymmetric) Key Type Shared secret (single key) RSA key pair (public + private) Security Good (if secret is protected) Better (private key never shared) Key Distribution Secret must be shared securely Public key can be distributed openly Token Verification Requires shared secret Uses public key (via JWKS) Key Rotation Requires secret update everywhere Seamless (JWKS supports multiple keys) Performance Faster (symmetric crypto) Slightly slower (asymmetric crypto) Use Case Simple deployments, testing Production, microservices JWKS Endpoint Not used Required (/.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
